妈妈  妈妈
Mom. mom. mom.
我逮着午餐食材了
I caught lunch.
是什么
What is it?
我不清楚  抓捕的过程发生的太快了
I don't know. it all went down pretty quick.
维克菲尔德女士
Mrs. wakefield.
给我们记上分吧
Put us on the scoreboard.
看起来鲁尼队
Looks like team rooney
今年干劲十足啊
Are the eager beavers this year.
那是故意说的俏皮话
Nature pun intended.
玛蒂
Maddie!
我来参加母女活动周啦
I am here for the mother-daughter weekend!
猜猜谁将要参加拓荒者聚会了啦
Who is ready to get their pioneer par-tay on?
噢  亲  你来这儿干什么啊
Oh, honey, what are you doing here?
我还以为这活动不适合你呢
I thought this wasn't your kind of thing.
对啊  再说了  我和妈妈都已经
Yeah, and besides, mom and I are already
组合好母女双人的一队了
Doing this together and it's only teams of two.
这就是为什么我出去凑了一个妈妈
That's why I went out and rustled up a mom.
一个妈妈
A mom?
你到底在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
哦  我指的是布丽·都蒙德
Oh, I'm just talking about Bree du monde.
布丽
Bree?
布丽·都蒙德是在《放声歌唱》里饰演
Bree du monde is the actress who played my mom
我妈妈的演员
On "sing it loud!"
她可是个三面手
She's a triple threat--
华丽的外表  前卫的时尚品味  疯狂的摇滚性格
Gor-gene, fab-smash, and rock-a-diculous.
哦  她来了
Oh! there she is now.
拓荒者布丽  听候大草原的指示
Pioneer bree, reporting to the prairie.
哦 忘记把坐骑锁上了
Oops, forgot to lock my horse.